It's special edition time today because I have some new Hirogato catsuits and they
have crazy patterns and colors which I wanted to show you. So yeah I've got a
bodysuit with integrated gloves here and I got a back zip catsuit with this really really
spacey cool metallic color design. So really looking forward to that one.
I hope you enjoy it, leave a thumbs up and I'll see you when I changed it.
First outfit. I think this is such a fun outfit because it looks really cool.
It looks kind of like an 80s movie. Now I could do some sports with that high cut here in the legs.
It definitely looks dynamic and I had a bit of a problem finding some tights for underneath
because the leg cut out here is really high so every time I tried some normal tights you
could tell that the hemline was here and it showed.
I wanted it now.
So I took these leggings and I took some tape and I taped them to my body which you can
ear so they stay in place and it also gives kind of nice corset look so yeah tips and tricks
i love the attached gloves because it looks kind of alien a bit but i also love the color
and so i think it's a really cool look if there wouldn't be gloves it wouldn't look that good
at least in my opinion so yeah and they're really comfy so the arms are really long
it's not too stretched here not too short so perfectly comfortable as with the whole bodysuit
i mean it is made to measure also the other ones if you are looking for made to measure
catsuits or spanish wear check out Hirogato i can definitely recommend it
so I think it's time for the second outfit also I can tell that the duct tape is coming loose so
yeah I won't have that problem with the catsuit let's change I am obsessed with this material
because it's so cool it's like shiny and metallic and it has a nice pattern all in one
In Germany we would say it's the Eierlegende Wollmilchsau because it also fits really good.
So something that ticks all the boxes basically.
Again I have to say it's made to measure so it does fit just superior.
I also noticed that it has a two-way sip in the crotch area which is new.
It was one way earlier in the past.
Now it's two way.
They also have new zipper...sips?
I don't know how do you call it?
The part where you pull?
So they look really nice
But yeah, this is for everyone who's asking how do you go to the toilet with that
Good zipper!
It's not that hard
It makes life so much more easy
Anyway
It does remind me a bit of Mystique from X-Men
because it's kind of blue and I don't know if my hair is also blue. I also like that we have
integrated socks here and the legs are still long enough so it's always more comfy if the socks are
integrated somehow. It also looks a bit of a northern lights area here I don't know with all
the light blue stripes and we have like teeny tiny dots everywhere in this
metallic look that's where the shine comes from this is a special edition
fabric as well as this one I also want to show you this one again because it's
also a really really nice color with a kind of holographic effect I think you
couldn't see that earlier when I wore it so here we go with the close-up I'm
I'm fascinated by this pattern.
I can look at it all the time and always think
that it looks like something different on you.
So I totally like this.
Really, really cool.
That's basically why I did another Hirogato video
because I just wanted to show you these fabrics
when I saw them I was like,
I have to have one with this nice fabric,
something out of the usual, not only one color.
So check out their homepage.
I'll link it in the description text.
And I will see you in the next video. Hope you enjoyed this one. Bye